<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disorientation on Moral Rights</title><link>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/</link><description>Recent content in Disorientation on Moral Rights</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Demographic Directions</title><link>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/demographic-directions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/demographic-directions/</guid><description>THe main flaw of Democratic ideology is the theory of demographic direction. Political campaigns are framed in terms of directions. The North vs the South, the East vs the West. Those are the geocentric discriminators of the &amp;ldquo;moral compass&amp;rdquo; political campains. Then there is the color-coded Blacks vs the Whites, or Reds vs Greens that supposedly represent demographic collectives. There are several more types of demographic campaigns. The real, everlasting political discriminator is based on a moral discriminator of Rights vs Wrongs, and that should be expressed in an always-available egocentric coordinate: what is Right and what should be Left.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/timeline-of-democrat-fascism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/timeline-of-democrat-fascism/</guid><description>Timeline of Democrat Fascism Outlaw guns fix prices New Deal economic tyrrany segregation persecute journalists property forfiture concentration camps rounding up into &amp;ldquo;reservations&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Disorientation Agenda</title><link>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/disorientation-agenda/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://moralrights.tech/disorientation/disorientation-agenda/</guid><description>Any discussion about politics must acknowlege that some portion of the must have a beligerent agenda.
We know that people make war. We must not assume that wars always happen by accident, or as the result of a misunderstanding between two peoples.
Some of them must be the product of a prior, internal, misunderstanding held by one of the beligerents: the belief that he benefits by war-making.</description></item></channel></rss>